grammymusic.net 2011-09-05

# Privacy Policy - GrammyMusic.net

##   Privacy Policy

Grammy Music is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please take a moment to read our policy explaining our use of the personal information that you provide and the choices you can make about the collection and use of your information by Grammy Music.

Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website. This Privacy Policy does not contain information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the website.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms of Use , as your use of the website constitutes your agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

From time to time, we may make changes to the guidelines and content of our policy. These changes will always be posted at this location on our website along with the date the changes were made. Your continued access of the website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy, so we encourage you to periodically review this policy in order to keep yourself fully informed of our privacy policy information.

CONTACT US

GrammyMusic.com is owned and operated by Grammy Music LLC ("Grammy Music"). If you have any questions concerning this policy or the content and material on our website, or if you would like to update your personal information, you may contact us at:

Grammy Music Magazine

Attention: Customer Relations, GrammyMusic.com

1290 Avenue of the Americas

New York, NY 10104

You may email us if you have questions about your privacy by emailing [suggestionbox@GrammyMusic.com](mailto:suggestionbox@GrammyMusic.com).

PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION

At GrammyMusic.com, we provide many interactive features which allow you to vote in polls, provide commentary on our features, participate in online forums, register for an account, and subscribe to our magazine online. While you may use many of the features of the website without providing any personal information, we may at times ask that you provide us with certain information so that we may perform the service you request.

This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail or home address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, birth date, gender, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

We will never collect personal information from you without your knowledge or consent, and you may always choose not to provide the information we request. Please note, however, that if you do not provide us with this information, you may be unable to access some of the features of the website.

HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION

From time to time, we may use the personal information you provide us to send you information regarding Grammy Music magazine and/or GrammyMusic.com features and subscriptions and/or to fulfill your requests for products, services and inquiries. We may use the information to contact you about your account or to notify you in the event that you win one of our contests or sweepstakes. We may also offer you or communicate with you about other products, programs, features, or services that we believe may be of interest to you. You will always have the choice to opt out of receiving these offers, updates, and information.

Unless otherwise specified on the website, we may sell or share personally identifying information with our affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the website that that may be managed or participated in by third parties, such as shopping areas. In such cases, the information may be used by us and those third parties, as well as with any participating sponsors or advertisers of such opportunities and features, each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While Grammy Music will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, Grammy Music does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of other third parties.

If you choose to purchase items through features on the website, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment.

We may disclose personal information when required by law to do so, for example, at the request of a law enforcement agency or when compelled by a court order or subpoena to do so.

If you submit written content, for example, a comment on a posting or a letter to the editor, to GrammyMusic.com, we may publish information about you that you provide, such as your name, username, and hometown along with your content.

NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

We may collect non-personally identifiable information, for example, the type of operating system you use to access our website, the domain name of your internet service provider, the type of browser you are using and your internet protocol ("IP") address. We use this information to improve many of the features of GrammyMusic.com; we may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage and to provide data to our advertisers.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our website.

While your personally identifying information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

INFORMATION FOR PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 13

We do not seek to collect personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received such information online from a child under the age of 13, we will delete it from our records. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to us. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of 13 who has provided personally identifiable information to us, please inform us by contacting us at the email address or telephone number listed above and we will remove such information from our database. If you are concerned about your children’s use of the Site, you may use web filtering technology to supervise or limit access to the Site

YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS (As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83)

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a Privacy Policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this Privacy Policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise the right.

As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure – typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our sites. If you do ask us to share your information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific promotion, as we do not share information with any third party on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personally identifiable information on one of our sites. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [suggestionbox@GrammyMusic.com](mailto:suggestionbox@GrammyMusic.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

COOKIES

We use cookies, as well as other tracking programs, for various features on GrammyMusic.com. A "Cookie" is a small data file that is able to store certain information when you visit a website. We may use cookies to perform such services as saving your password in password-protected areas and remembering your video plug-in preferences so that you do not have to reset them each time you visit our site. We may also use cookies to track how often visitors are visiting GrammyMusic.com, which pages are visited most often, and user preferences. Cookies will not allow us access to personal information which you have not already provided to us. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so by turning them off in your web browser. While many parts of GrammyMusic.com will still be accessible to you if you choose to disable cookies, you may be unable to use certain features of the website.

SECURITY INFORMATION

We take the protection of your personal information seriously. Our databases are stored in a secure location and your information is guarded by firewalls and other technology. Although we take appropriate precautions to ensure the security of your information, we cannot assure you that the personal information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING AND WEBSITES

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit GrammyMusic.com. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to our website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please visit http://www.doubleclick.com/contact/index.aspx.

GrammyMusic.com may contain links to other websites. The privacy policies of these websites may be different than those listed here, and we do not have any control over, and are not responsible for, the information or use of this information that these websites collect. Please read the privacy notices of any third party websites for their policies.

From time to time, GrammyMusic.com may offer promotions, contests, or sweepstakes that are sponsored or co-sponsored by other companies. These companies may have access to the personal information you provide in order to participate in these promotions, sweepstakes, or contests. We do not have any control over, and are not responsible for, our sponsors' or co-sponsors' use of this information.

We may also use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the Website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Grammy Music disclaims all liability in connection therewith. If you do not want the benefits of these advertising cookies, you may be able to opt-out by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.
